[
    {
        "module":1,
        "question":"What does JVM stand for?",
        "answers":["Java Virtual Machine", "Java Visualization Methods", "Jesuits Visiting Maryland", "Java’s Very Majestic"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":1,
        "question":"Why is the JVM useful?",
        "answers":["It makes Java platform independent", "It purges the system of filthy python code", "It proactively patches runtime errors", "It makes syntax cleaner"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":1,
        "question":"How can you store the value \"8.0\"?",
        "answers":["double boi = 8.0;", "int boi = 8.0", "String boi = 8.0", "ArrayList<TriangularBois>> boi = 8.0"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":1,
        "question":"Which is the correct method header?",
        "answers":["public static void main(String[] args)", "public void static main(String[] args)", "public static main(String args)", "public"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":1,
        "question":"What are the two basic aspects of programming?",
        "answers":["Data and Instructions", "Loops and Variables", "Logic and Syntax", "Logic and Variables"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":1,
        "question":"Which boolean expression will return false?",
        "answers":["(3 <= 2)", "(‘a’ == ‘a’ )", "(9.1 > 8.9)", "(2 < 5)"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which is the smallest data type?",
        "answers":["short", "int", "byte", "long"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which is the largest data type?",
        "answers":["long", "int", "byte", "char"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which is not a primitive data type?",
        "answers":["String", "char", "float", "int"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which is not a primitive data type?",
        "answers":["String", "double", "float", "int"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which is not a primitive data type?",
        "answers":["String", "short", "boolean", "int"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which is incorrect?",
        "answers":["char c = a;", "char c = ‘a’;", "char c = ‘3’;", "char c = ‘?’;"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which is incorrect?",
        "answers":["char c = \"v\";", "char c = ‘v’;", "char c = ‘9’;", "char c = ‘\\n’;"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which is incorrect?",
        "answers":["char c = ‘hi’;", "char c = ‘a’;", "char c = ‘ ’;", "char c = ‘\\t’;"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which is incorrect?",
        "answers":["int i = 30.9;", "int i = 2;", "String s = \"30.9\";", "double d = 3;"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"What will this print, if var = \"blah\"? System.out.print(\"Hello\" + var + \"Bye!\");",
        "answers":["HelloblahBye!", "Hello blah bye!", "Hello blah Bye!", "HelloblahBye"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"What will this print, if String var = \"blah\":  System.out.print(\"Hello\\t\" + var + \"\\tBye!\");",
        "answers":["Hello     blah     Bye!", "Hello blah Bye!", "Hello\\tblah\\tBye!", "Hello\\t blah \\tBye!"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"What will this print?  System.out.print(\"1+2+3\");",
        "answers":["1+2+3", "\"1+2+3\"", "123", "6"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"What will this print?  System.out.print(\"1\" + \"2\" + \"3\");",
        "answers":["123", "\"1\" + \"2\" + \"3\"", "1 + 2 + 3", "6"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"What will this print?  System.out.print(1+2+3);",
        "answers":["6", "\"1+2+3\"", "123", "1+2+3"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"What will this print?  System.out.print(1+a+3);",
        "answers":["6", "\"1+2+3\"", "123", "1+2+3"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"How do you get user input?",
        "answers":["Use a Scanner", "System.out.print()", "System.in.print()", "cin << x"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which Scanner set-up is correct?",
        "answers":["Scanner scnr = new Scanner(System.in);", "Scanner = new Scanner(System.in);", "Scanner scnr = Scanner(System.in);", "scanf(System.in(cin<<x)).in;"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int h = 9; int i = h++; What is the value of i?",
        "answers":["10", "9", "11", "9.1"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int i = 0; int j = ++i; What is the value of j?",
        "answers":["1", "2", "-1", "0.1"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int h = -5; int i = h++; What is the value of i?",
        "answers":["-4", "5", "-6", "-3"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int i = -16; int j = ++i; What is the value of j?",
        "answers":["-15", "-17", "16", "-14"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int h = 9; int i = h--; What is the value of i?",
        "answers":["8", "10", "-9", "8.9"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int i = 0; int j = --i; What is the value of j?",
        "answers":["-1", "1", "0", "0.1"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int h = -5; int i = h--; What is the value of i?",
        "answers":["-6", "5", "-4", "-3"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int i = -41; int j = --i; What is the value of j?",
        "answers":["-42", "41", "-40", "40"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 9, and int b = 2. What is the value of the expression (a!=b)?",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 7, and int b = 2. What is the value of the expression (a==b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 9, and double b = 9.0. What is the value of the expression (a==b)?",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"double a = 4.4, and int b = 4. What is the value of the expression (a==b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 9, and int b = 8. What is the value of the expression (a==b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"double a = 4.0, and int b = 4. What is the value of the expression (a=!b)?",
        "answers":["invalid syntax", "true", "runtime error", "false"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 4, and char b = ‘4’. What is the value of the expression (a==b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid code", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 6, and char b = ‘4’. What is the value of the expression (a==b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid code", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"double a = 4.9, and char b = ‘4’. What is the value of the expression (a==b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid code", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 8, and int b = 2. What is the value of the expression (a!=b)?",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 8, and int b = 22. What is the value of the expression (a!=b)?",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 8, and int b = 8. What is the value of the expression (a!=b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 7, and int b = 2. What is the value of the expression (a<b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 9, and double b = 9.0. What is the value of the expression (a>b)?",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"double a = 4.4, and int b = 4. What is the value of the expression (a>b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 9, and int b = 8. What is the value of the expression (a<b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid syntax", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"double a = 4.0, and int b = 4. What is the value of the expression (a=>b)?",
        "answers":["invalid syntax", "true", "runtime error", "false"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 4, and char b = ‘4’. What is the value of the expression (a>=b)?",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid code", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"int a = 6, and char b = ‘4’. What is the value of the expression (a<=b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid code", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"double a = 4.9, and char b = ‘4’. What is the value of the expression (a>=b)?",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid code", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"String a = \"allardice\", and String b = \"mattson\". What is the value of the expression (a>b)?",
        "answers":["invalid code", "false", "true", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"String a = \"Java\", and String b = \"Python\". What is the value of the expression (a==b)?",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid code", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"String a = \"Java\", and String b = \"Java\". What is the value of the expression (a==b)?",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid code", "runtime error"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"What does the following symbol mean?  &&  ",
        "answers":["Boolean AND", "Boolean OR", "Boolean NOT", "Boo! It’s a ghost"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"What does the following symbol mean?  ||  ",
        "answers":["Boolean OR", "Boolean AND", "Boolean NOT", "Boolean Eleven"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"What does the following symbol mean?  !  ",
        "answers":["Boolean NOT", "Boolean OR", "Boolean AND", "Exclamation mark used by the JVM to denote angry, horrified screaming at the runtime errors generated by inexperienced programmers."],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 0:  !!(x>1)",
        "answers":["False", "True", "big oof", "Invalid code"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 0:  (x==0)!!!!!!!!! ",
        "answers":["Invalid syntax", "True", "X EQUALS ZERO!!!!!!!!!", "true, but yelled really loudly"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 0 and y = 4: ((x>=0) && (y>5))",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid code", "your mom"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 1 and y = 1: ((x>=0) || (y>5))",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid code", "do you think if we asked really nicely, tim mattson would come speak at GCC?"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 1 and y = 4: ((x>=0) && !(y>5))",
        "answers":["true", "false", "invalid code", "panicked screech"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 8 and y = -7: (!(x>=0) && (y<5))",
        "answers":["false", "true", "invalid code", "panicked screech"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 5: x%3",
        "answers":["2", "1/2", "5/3", "1"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 2: x%17",
        "answers":["2", "2/17", "7", "-1"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 1 and y = 4: x%y",
        "answers":["1", "1/4", "2", "0"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 10 and y = 4: x%y",
        "answers":["2", "5/2", "6", "1"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 1: x%2",
        "answers":["1", "1/2", "2", "0"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 2: x%2",
        "answers":["0", "1/2", "2", "1"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Evaluate the following statement, if x = 8: x%2",
        "answers":["0", "4", "2", "6"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Given int a, double x, and short b, which type conversion is illegal if A = 16?",
        "answers":["b = a", "x = a", "x = 16.0", "a = 11"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Given int a, double x, and short b, which type conversion is illegal if a = 11?",
        "answers":["b = a", "x = a", "b=(short)a", "x = (double)a"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Given int a, double x, and char b, which type conversion is illegal if a = 1?",
        "answers":["b = a", "b = (char)a", "x = a", "a += 11"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which operator takes precedence in an expression?",
        "answers":["unary", "multiplication", "division", "addition"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which operator takes precedence in an expression?",
        "answers":["subtraction", "equality", "inequality", "boolean OR"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which operator takes precedence in an expression?",
        "answers":["equality", "boolean AND", "conditional operator", "assignment operator"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which operator takes precedence in an expression?",
        "answers":["++", "&&", "||", "%="],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":2,
        "question":"Which operator takes precedence in an expression?",
        "answers":["*/", "+", "!=", "+="],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"An array uses what type of indexing?",
        "answers":["Zero-indexing", "One-indexing"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"The individual items in an Array are ___ of the Array.",
        "answers":["Base Types", "Child Types", "Subtypes", "Main Types"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"Which statement correctly creates an Array of Strings?",
        "answers":["list = new String[5]", "new list = String[5]", "new String = list[5]", "new String[5] = list"],
        "bloomValue":2
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"The position in an Array is called the length.",
        "answers":["False", "True"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"Arrays can have multiple base types in one Array.",
        "answers":["False", "True"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"A simple way to parse through an Array is to use a...",
        "answers":["For Loop", "While Loop", "Do-While Loop", "none of the above"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"What is the most common mistake when going through an Array with a For Loop?",
        "answers":["Indexing out of range", "Reading data", "Creating items", "Writing to console"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"What is the expection received whenever the index of an Array is exceeded?",
        "answers":["ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException", "IntegerExpectedException", "CloneNotSupportedException", "IllegalAccessException"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"How many items in an Array are read by \"for(int i = 8; i >= 0; i--)\"?",
        "answers":["9", "8", "0", "10"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"A two-dimensional Array must use the same base type for each dimension of the Array.",
        "answers":["True", "False"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"In int[5][5] nums, if you want to access the 3rd item in the 4th list, the index would be...",
        "answers":["[3][2]", "[3][4]", "[2][3]", "[4][3]"],
        "bloomValue":2
    },
    {
        "module":4,
        "question":"If a two-dimensional Array has a max index of [8][9], how many values are in the Array?",
        "answers":["90", "72", "89", "17"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"Subroutines are often referred to as...",
        "answers":["Methods", "Classes", "Objects", "Interfaces"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"To access a property of a class you use a(n)...",
        "answers":["Dot Operator", "Colon", "Semicolon", "Apostrophe"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"A variable can hold an object.",
        "answers":["False", "True"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"If std is a Student object, how would you declare std to be an empty object?",
        "answers":["std = null", "std = none", "std = empty", "std = 0"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"Methods that return a variable of a class are called...",
        "answers":["getters", "setters", "mutators", "returners"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"Every class has a Constructor.",
        "answers":["True", "False"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"When calling a constructor, what form does the expression have?",
        "answers":["new className(parameters)", "new className", "className(parameters)", "new(className)(parameters)"],
        "bloomValue":2
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"Object.toString() returns...",
        "answers":["A string representing Object", "A string with the properties of Object", "The hashcode of Object"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"In Inheritance, the class inheriting structure and behavior is the...",
        "answers":["subclass", "superclass", "mini-class", "none of the above"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"In Inheritance, the class giving inheritance is the...",
        "answers":["superclass", "subclass", "hyper-class", "none of the above"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"A set of classes that are related forms a...",
        "answers":["Class Hierarchy", "Class Family", "Class Nucleus", "Class House"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"Which statement uses \"this\" correctly?",
        "answers":["this.name = name", "name = this.name", "name.this = this", "name.this = name"],
        "bloomValue":2
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"Which statement uses \"super\" correctly?",
        "answers":["super.roll()", "roll().super", "roll(super)", "super(roll)"],
        "bloomValue":2
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"Multiple Inheritance is allowed in Java.",
        "answers":["False", "True"],
        "bloomValue":1
    },
    {
        "module":6,
        "question":"How many interfaces can a Java class implement?",
        "answers":["Infinite", "One", "Ten", "Three"],
        "bloomValue":1
    }
]
